question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "AMC's 'The Walking Dead', Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and "
                    "Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Snakes and Ladders was originally created in India?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Arcade Fire's 'The Suburbs' won the Album of the Year award in the 2011 Grammys.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "This is the correct spelling of 'Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious'.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Kangaroos keep food in their pouches next to their children.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Faust is a playable character in 'Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator'.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in 'Clash Royale'.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
